# KENTO HONDA

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

+1 (604) 671-3832 | kentos1112canada@gmail.com | Portfolio website | LinkedIn | GitHub

### **SUMMARY:**

Web developer with +1 year of equivalent experience mainly in the FrontEnd field including work experience in my current company, my personal projects, and school projects. A quick learner and coding lover with an insatiable passion for self-improvement to grow more as a web developer.

### **SKILLS:**

ReactJS | NextJS | Javascript(ES6) | Typescript | Redux | NodeJS | Express | HTML5 | CSS3 | SASS | Styled Components | Material UI | Chakra UI | Ant Design | Tailwind CSS | Bootstrap | jQuery | AJAX | MongoDB | Firebase | PostgreSQL | GraphQL | Jest | RESTful API | Git

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

#### BuildN | FrontEnd Developer | 01 September, 2022 - Present | Vancouver, BC

<u>Developing the FrontEnd part of BuildN's corporate web application with NextJS, Typescript, and Jira as the task management tool.</u> Also, working as teams including collaborations with designers and BackEnd developers. Mainly I am in charge of creating reusable UI components, and functions connecting to the BackEnd part (API). Based on agile development, I handle sprint meetings every two weeks to enhance the quality of applications as well as work efficiencies.

### SMC Corporation | Salesperson | 01 April, 2017 - 31 September, 2021 | Tokyo, Japan

Applied professional problem-solving skills to solve issues that clients had, resulting in increasing 20% sales by introducing appropriate products that I promoted.

#### PROJECTS:

#### ShoppingList-Mern-App | ReactJS, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, ChakraUI, bcrypt, JWT

- MERN-stack application memorizing shopping items with MongoDB, Express, React, and NodeJS.
- Showcasing my skills such as developing a full-stack application with a good understanding of bcrypt and JWT, connecting MongoDB to React App, and styling with Chakra UI.

#### StudyLog | Typescript, ReactJS, Firebase, Tailwind CSS, Ant Design Chart, MerakiUI

- Helpful web application that analyzes and visualizes users' daily study records.
- Utilized Ant Design Chart to visualize data with line charts and manipulated users' data with firebase.

## <u>CountryBeen</u> | Typescript, ReactJS, Redux, Firebase, TailwindCSS, DaisyUI

- Useful web application for remembering countries where users have been before.
- Applied Redux toolkit for state management with Typescript, and a React library (react-simple-map).

## <u>FreshMarche</u> | ReactJS, Firebase, MaterialUI, Stripe API

- E-commerce-like application specializing in fruits and vegetables created with ReactJS and MaterialUI.
- Implemented CRUD operations with React-Router, applied Stripe API for the checkout section.

## **Doctor Appointment** | ReactJS, Redux, MongoDB, Firebase, Styled-components

- Group project in school Practical application for booking doctor appointments.
- Completed connecting React App to MongoDB, as well as utilizing firebase for user authentication.

#### **EDUCATION:**

#### 2021 - 2022 | Cornerstone International Community College of Canada

Web Development - Diploma | Learned fundamentals of programming and experienced multiple team projects for gaining practical experience.

#### 2012 - 2017 | Shiga University

**Bachelor of Science in Economics**